Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2017 RL.00924
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2011; 2399 Volumes
  - Star Patrol, 120
    - Mission Master Pack (no city: Terra Games Company), undated (Volume M5)
  - Star Trek, 121
    - A Doomsday Like Any Other (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1238)
    - A Fragile Peace: The Neutral Zone Campaign Vol. 1 (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1998 (Volume 1949)
    - A Matter of Priorities (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1230)
    - Aliens (Los Angeles, CA: Decipher, Inc.), 2003 (Volume 2249)
    - All Our Yesterdays: The Time Travel Sourcebook (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1934)
    - Among the Clans: The Andorians (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1940)
    - An Imbalance of Power (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1207)
    - Conflict of Interests (Including Klingon Intelligence Briefing) (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1208)
    - Creatures (Los Angeles, CA: Decipher, Inc.), 2003 (Volume 2248)
    - Decision at Midnight (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1206)
    - Demand of Honor (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1227)
    - Denial of Destiny (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1983 (Volume 1226)
    - Graduation Exercise (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1231)
    - Holodeck Adventures (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1942)
    - Klingon: Ship Recognition Manual (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1213)
    - Margin of Profit (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1159)
    - Margin of Profit (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1224)
    - Narrator's Guide (Norfolk, VA: Decipher, Inc.), 2002 (Volume 1938)
    - Narrator's Toolkit (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1941)
    - Narrator's Toolkit (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1944)
    - Orion Ruse (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1225)
    - Player's Guide (Norfolk, VA: Decipher, Inc.), 2002 (Volume 1936)
    - Raiders, Renegades & Rogues (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1939)
    - Regula-1: Orbital Station Deckplans (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 978)
    - Return to Axanar (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1203)
    - Romulan: Ship Recognition Manual (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1212)
    - Star Fleet Intelligence Manual: Agent's Orientation Sourcebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 1221)
    - Star Fleet Intelligence Manual: Game Operation (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 1220)
    - Star Trek III: Sourcebook Update (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1229)
    - Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home: Sourcebook Update (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 979)
    - Star Trek Roleplaying Game: Core Game Book (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1943)
    - Star Trek Roleplaying Game: Narrator's Screen (Norfolk, VA: Decipher, Inc.), 2002 (Volume 1933)
    - Star Trek: Deep Space Nine Roleplaying Game, Core Game Book (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1935)
    - Star Trek: The Next Generation Role Playing Game: Core Game Book (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1998 (Volume 1952)
    - Star Trek: The Next Generation Role Playing Game: Narrator's Toolkit (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1998 (Volume 1953)
    - Star Trek: The Next Generation: First Year Sourcebook (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1989 (Volume 977)
    - Star Trek: The Next Generation: Planetary Adventures, Volume 1: Federation Space (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1946)
    - Star Trek: The Next Generation: Planets of the UFP Sourcebook (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1947)
    - Star Trek: The Next Generation: Player's Guide (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1999 (Volume 1945)
    - Starfleet Operations Manual (Norfolk, VA: Decipher, Inc.), 2003 (Volume 1937)
    - Starships (Los Angeles, CA: Decipher, Inc.), 2003 (Volume 2250)
    - Termination: 1456 (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1228)
    - The Dixie Gambit (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 980)
    - The Federation (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1222)
    - The First Line: Starfleet Intelligence Handbook (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1998 (Volume 1951)
    - The Four Years War: A Concise Compilation of Library Information (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1204)
    - The Klingons: Game Operation Manual (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 1211)
    - The Klingons: Star Fleet Intelligence Manual (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 1210)
    - The Mines of Selka (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1986 (Volume 1237)
    - The Orions: Book of Common Knowledge (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 1217)
    - The Orions: Book of Deep Knowledge (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 1216)
    - The Outcasts (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1223)
    - The Price of Freedom: The United Federation of Planets Sourcebook (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1998 (Volume 1948)
    - The Romulan Way: Game Operations Manual (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1233)
    - The Romulan Way: Game Operations Manual (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1234)
    - The Romulans (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1236)
    - The Romulans: Starfleet Ingelligence Manual (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1984 (Volume 1235)
    - The Strider Incident (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 983)
    - The Triangle (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1218)
    - The Vanished (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1983 (Volume 1214)
    - The Way of Kolinahr: The Vulcans (Culver City, CA: Last Unicorn Games), 1998 (Volume 1950)
    - Trader Captains and Merchant Princes (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1983 (Volume 1209)
    - Trader Captains and Merchant Princes (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1987 (Volume 1219)
    - Triangle Campaign (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1232)
    - Where Has All the Glory Gone? (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1985 (Volume 1205)
    - Witness for the Defense (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1983 (Volume 1215)
  - Star Wars, 122
    - A New Hope: Galaxy Guide 1 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1864)
    - Adventure Journal, Issues 1-4 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1824)
    - Alien Anthology (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1835)
    - Alien Encounters (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1998 (Volume 1885)
    - Alien Races: Galaxy Guide 4 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1861)
    - Alliance Intelligence Reports (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1813)
    - Arms and Equipment Guide (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 1830)
    - Battle for the Golden Sun (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1988 (Volume 1872)
    - Black Ice (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1867)
    - Campaign Pack (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1988 (Volume 1877)
    - Character Record Sheets (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 1843)
    - Classic Adventures, Vol. 1 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1823)
    - Classic Adventures, Vol. 2 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1822)
    - Classic Adventures, Vol. 3 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1821)
    - Classic Adventures, Volume Four: The Best of the Journal (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1905)
    - Classic Campaigns` (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1820)
    - Core Rulebook (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 1841)
    - Coruscant and the Core Worlds (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 1828)
    - Cracken's Rebel Field Guide (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1991 (Volume 1845)
    - Cracken's Rebel Operatives (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1812)
    - Cracken's Threat Dossier (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1898)
    - Creatures of the Galaxy (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1815)
    - Crisis on Cloud City (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1865)
    - Cynabar's Fantastic Techonolgy: Droids (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1903)
    - Dark Empire Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1925)
    - Dark Force Rising Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1927)
    - Death In the Undercity (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1857)
    - Death Star Technical Companion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1991 (Volume 1849)
    - Death Star: Technical Companion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1816)
    - Domain of Evil (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1991 (Volume 1855)
    - Endgame (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1809)
    - Flashpoint!: Brak Sector (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1799)
    - Galactic Campaign Guide (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 2247)
    - Galaxy Guide 1: A New Hope (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1918)
    - Galaxy Guide 10: Bounty Hunters (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1909)
    - Galaxy Guide 11: Criminal Organizations (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1908)
    - Galaxy Guide 12: Aliens, Enemies and Allies (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1907)
    - Galaxy Guide 2: Yavin and Bespin, Revised and Expanded (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1917)
    - Galaxy Guide 3: The Empire Strikes Back (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1916)
    - Galaxy Guide 4: Alien Races (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1915)
    - Galaxy Guide 5: Return of the Jedi (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1914)
    - Galaxy Guide 6: Tramp Freighters (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1913)
    - Galaxy Guide 7: Mos Eisley (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1912)
    - Galaxy Guide 8: Scouts (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1911)
    - Galaxy Guide 9: Fragments from the Rim (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1910)
    - Galladinium's Fatastic Technology: Guns and Gear for Any Occasion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1814)
    - Gamemaster Handbook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1818)
    - Gamemaster Kit (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1991 (Volume 1854)
    - Gamemaster Screen (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1819)
    - Gamemaster Screen (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1842)
    - Geonosis and the Outer Rim Worlds (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2004 (Volume 2245)
    - Goroth: Slave of the Empire (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1806)
    - Graveyard of Alderaan (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1991 (Volume 1856)
    - Gundark's Fantastic Technology: Personal Gear (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1895)
    - Hans Solo and the Corporate Sector Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1921)
    - Heir to the Empire Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1928)
    - Hero's Guide (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 1826)
    - Heroes and Rogues (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1798)
    - Hideouts & Strongholds (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1998 (Volume 1884)
    - Imperial Double-Cross (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1906)
    - Imperial Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1880)
    - Imperial Sourcebook, Second Edition (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1923)
    - Instant Adventures (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1904)
    - Jedi's Honor (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1876)
    - Live-Action Adventures (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1825)
    - Living Force: Campaign Guide (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1839)
    - Minatures Battles (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1932)
    - Minatures Battles: Companion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1931)
    - Minatures Battles: Imperial Entanglements (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1930)
    - Mission to Lianna (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1846)
    - No Disintegrations: Adventures for bounty hunters! (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1902)
    - Operation: Elrood (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1899)
    - Otherspace (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1871)
    - Otherspace II: Invasion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1868)
    - Planet of the Mists (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1848)
    - Planets Collection (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1807)
    - Planets of the Galaxy, Vol. 1 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1991 (Volume 1853)
    - Planets of the Galaxy, Vol. 2 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1852)
    - Planets of the Galaxy, Vol. 3 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1851)
    - Platt's Smugglers Guide (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1889)
    - Platt's Starport Guide (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1995 (Volume 1808)
    - Power of the Jedi Sourcebook (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 1829)
    - Privates and Privateers (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1901)
    - Rebel Alliance Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1879)
    - Rebel Alliance Sourcebook, Second Edition (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1924)
    - Rebellion Era Sourcebook (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1836)
    - Return of the Jedi: Galaxy Guide 5 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1860)
    - Revised Core Rulebook (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 1831)
    - Riders of the Maelstrom (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1869)
    - Rules Companion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1878)
    - Rules of Engagement: The Rebel Specforce Handbook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1894)
    - Scavenger Hunt (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1870)
    - Secrets of Naboo (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1840)
    - Secrets of Tatooine (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1838)
    - Secrets of the Sisar Run (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1897)
    - Shadows of the Empire: Planets Guide (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1801)
    - Shadows of the Empire: Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1802)
    - Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1987 (Volume 1881)
    - Star Wars Classic Adventures Volume Five (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1998 (Volume 1891)
    - Star Wars Gamemaster Screen, Revised (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1893)
    - Star Wars Player's Guide to Tapani (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1892)
    - Star Wars Sourcebook, Second Edition (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1922)
    - Star Wars Tapani Sector Instant Adventures (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1890)
    - Star Wars The Roleplaying Game, Second Edition (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1929)
    - Star Wars Trilogy Sourcebook, Special Edition (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1888)
    - Starfall (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1873)
    - Starships of the Galaxy (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1834)
    - Stock Ships (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1886)
    - Strike Force: Shantipole (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1988 (Volume 1874)
    - Supernova (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1919)
    - Tales of the Jedi Companion (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1800)
    - Tatooine Manhunt (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1988 (Volume 1875)
    - Tempest Feud (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 1832)
    - The Abduction (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1850)
    - The Black Sands of Socorro (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1896)
    - The Dark Side Sourcebook (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2001 (Volume 1837)
    - The Empire Strikes Back: Galaxy Guide 3 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1862)
    - The Far Orbit Project (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1998 (Volume 1883)
    - The Game Chambers of Questal (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1866)
    - The Isis Coordinates (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1858)
    - The Jedi Academy Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1803)
    - The Kathol Outback (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1811)
    - The Kathol Rift (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1810)
    - The Last Command Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1994 (Volume 1926)
    - The Movie Trilogy Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1844)
    - The New Jedi Order Sourcebook (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 1833)
    - The Politics of Contraband (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1992 (Volume 1847)
    - The Roleplaying Game (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1987 (Volume 1882)
    - The Star Wars Roleplaying Game, Second Edition (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1887)
    - The Thrawn Trilogy Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1805)
    - The Truce at Bakura Sourcebook (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1996 (Volume 1804)
    - Tramp Freighters: Galaxy Guide 6 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1990 (Volume 1859)
    - Twin Stars of Kira (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1920)
    - Ultimate Adversaries (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2004 (Volume 2246)
    - Ultimate Alien Anthology (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2003 (Volume 1827)
    - Wanted by Cracken (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1993 (Volume 1817)
    - Wretched Hives of Scum and Villainy (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1997 (Volume 1900)
    - Yavin and Bespin: Galaxy Guide 2 (Honesdale, PA: West End Games), 1989 (Volume 1863)
  - Stormbringer, 123
    - Perils of the Young Kingdoms: Supernatural Battles Across the World of Elric (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 380)
    - Rogue Mistress (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 378)
    - Sea Kings of the Purple Towns (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 381)
    - Sorcerers of Pan Tang (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 379)
    - Stormbringer: Fantasy Roleplaying in the World of Elric, 4th edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 377)
  - Superworld & Champions, 124
    - Bad Medicine for Dr. Drugs (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1983 (Volume 2143)
  - Superworld, Villains and Vigilantes, & Champions, 125
    - Trouble for Havoc (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1984 (Volume 2142)
  - Supremacy, 126
    - Commander-in-Chief's Rule Book to Mega Supremacy: Challenge of the New World Order (Buffalo, NY: Supremacy Games, Inc. ), 1991 (Volume 642)
  - Tarantis, 127
    - Tarantis (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1454)
    - Tarantis: Levels 2-6 (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1693)
  - The Babylon Project, 128
    - Earthforce Sourcebook (Blacksburg, VA: WireFrame Productions), 1997 (Volume 47)
    - Gamemaster's Resource Kit (no place: WireFrame Productions), 1998 (Volume 45)
    - The Babylon Project: The Roleplaying Game Based on Babylon 5 (Blacksburg, VA: WireFrame Productions), 1997 (Volume 46)
  - The Fantasy Trip, 129
    - Advanced Melee (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1980 (Volume 1058)
    - Advanced Wizard (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1980 (Volume 1059)
    - Death Test (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1978 (Volume 683)
    - Fantasy Masters' Screen (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1981 (Volume 1057)
    - In the Labyrinth: Game Master's Module (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1980 (Volume 1060)
    - Melee (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1977 (Volume 676)
    - Melee (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1977 (Volume 682)
    - The Fantasy Masters' Codex (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1981 (Volume 1064)
    - Tollenkar's Lair: Adventure Supplement (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1980 (Volume 1063)
    - Wizard (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1978 (Volume 675)
  - The Hero System, 130
    - Cyber Hero (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 2263)
    - Fantasy Hero (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 2265)
    - Hero Bestiary (#507) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 2173)
    - Hero System Almanac 1 (#508) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1993 (Volume 2149)
    - Hero System Almanac 2 (#511) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1995 (Volume 2146)
    - Hero System Rulesbook (#500) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 2174)
    - Horror Hero: Endless Nightmares (#509) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1994 (Volume 2148)
    - The Hero System: Bestiary (#25) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1986 (Volume 2131)
    - The Ultimate Martial Artist (#510) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1994 (Volume 2147)
    - The Ultimate Mentalist (#512) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1995 (Volume 2160)
  - The Land Beyond the Mountains, 131
    - The Forest-Lords of Dihad (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1982 (Volume 1062)
    - The Warrior-Lords of Darok (Austin, TX: Metagaming ), 1982 (Volume 1061)
  - The Morrow Project, 132
    - The Morrow Project (Warren, MI: TimeLine, Ltd. ), 1980 (Volume 1078)
    - The Ruins of Chicago (Lansing, MI: TimeLine, Ltd.), 1983 (Volume 1079)
  - Thieves' Guild, 133
    - Bandit Gangs and Caravans (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd. ), 1983 (Volume 1740)
      2 copies
    - Thieves' Guild (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords Ltd.), 1980 (Volume M3)
    - Thieves' Guild 6 (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd. ), 1982 (Volume 1591)
    - Thieves' Guild 7 (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd. ), 1982 (Volume 1592)
    - Thieves' Guild 8 (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd. ), 1983 (Volume 1593)
    - Thieves' Guild 9: Escape from the Ashwood Mines (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords, Ltd. ), 1983 (Volume 1594)
    - Thieves' Guild III (Gaithersburg, MD: Gamelords Ltd.), 1981 (Volume M3)
  - Thieves' World, 134
    - Dark Assassin (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1982 (Volume 1610)
    - The Spirit Stones (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1982 (Volume 1611)
    - Traitor (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1982 (Volume 1612)
  - Timemaster, 135
    - Clash of Kings! A Tale of Arthur and Merlin (Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd. ), 1984 (Volume 1157)
    - Crossed Swords: With the Three Musketeers (Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd. ), 1984 (Volume 1153)
    - Partisans from the Shadows (Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd. ), 1984 (Volume 1156)
    - Sea Dogs of England (Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd. ), 1984 (Volume 1158)
    - The Cleopatra Gambit (Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd. ), 1984 (Volume 1154)
    - Timemaster Screen: Featuring Missing PT 109 (Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd. ), 1984 (Volume 1155)
    - Whom the Gods Destroy (Delavan, WI: Pacesetter, Ltd. ), 1985 (Volume 1160)
  - Tomes, 136
    - Axe of the Dwarvish Lords (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 926)
  - Top Secret, 137
    - Operation: Seventh Seal (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 441)
  - Top Secret: Espionage Adventure, 138
    - Ace of Clubs (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 442)
  - Top Secret: Espionage Game, 139
    - Lady in Distress (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 445)
    - Operation: Fastpass (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 444)
    - Operation: Orient Express (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 443)
    - Operation: Rapidstrike (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 446)
  - Top Secret/S.I., 140